globotreks.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy

GloboTreks is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Website. You can access GloboTreks and browse our site without disclosing any of your personal data. GloboTreks does not collect personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and he or she has agreed to the terms under which GloboTreks will use it.

Your privacy is critically important to us. At GloboTreks we have a few fundamental principles:

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)

We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:[](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) (Note, we’ve decided to make this privacy policy available under a  **Creative Commons Sharealike** license, which means you’re more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use, just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you, and if you want we’d appreciate a link to our site somewhere on your site. We spent a lot of money and time on the below, and other people shouldn’t need to do the same.)

GloboTreks is operated by Fuse Concepts Inc. It is GloboTreks’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, GloboTreks collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. GloboTreks’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how GloboTreks’ visitors use its website. From time to time, GloboTreks may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

GloboTreks also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. GloboTreks does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to GloboTreks’ websites choose to interact with GloboTreks in ways that require GloboTreks to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that GloboTreks gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a newsletter to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with GloboTreks are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, GloboTreks collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with GloboTreks. GloboTreks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

GloboTreks may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. GloboTreks may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, GloboTreks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

GloboTreks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GloboTreks’ behalf or to provide services available at GloboTreks’ websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using GloboTreks’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. GloboTreks will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, GloboTreks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when GloboTreks believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GloboTreks, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a GloboTreks website and have supplied your email address, GloboTreks may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with GloboTreks and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GloboTreks takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. GloboTreks uses cookies to help GloboTreks identify and track visitors, their usage of GloboTreks website, and their website access preferences. GloboTreks visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GloboTreks’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of GloboTreks’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by GloboTreks and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Affiliate Program Participation**

GloboTreks may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link to an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

GloboTreks is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

**Disclosure of Information**

GloboTreks will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information, track userís movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

If you do not want to have your information used in this way, send an e-mail message containing your name and email address to globotreks@gmail.com. GloboTreks may release account information when such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law; enforce the terms of any of our user agreements; or protect the rights, property, and safety of GloboTreks, the users of its site, or others.

**Rights Related to Your Personal Information**

_Opt-out_ – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at globotreks@gmail.com to be removed from our mailing list.

_Access_ – You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to globotreks@gmail.com.

_Amend_ – You may contact us at globotreks@gmail.com to amend or update your personal information.

_Forget_ – In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to globotreks@gmail.com.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for record-keeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our sites from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under 18.

**External Web Sites**

Please note that GloboTreks contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site that you read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information.

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by GloboTreks. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact: globotreks@gmail.com

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, GloboTreks may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in GloboTreks’ sole discretion. GloboTreks encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Last updated: 01/2019

[Contact us](https://www.globotreks.com/contact-me/) if you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data.

You can also read the [Terms of Use](https://www.globotreks.com/terms/) of this website.
